to you. Good day.
>> Much love
>> and to you as well.
>> A couple of questions for you. One is
based in religion and the other in
science and medicine and innovation.
>> So
>> guys,
>> with regards to religion, some of the
major leaders, could you expand or
expound a little bit on Moses?
>> What does Moses have to do with
religion?
I guess I'm asking you that he was a
major leader that was a figure within
the Old Testament.
>> We understand who you're referring to,
>> but the way we ask that question should
be very revealing to you because Moses
doesn't have to have anything at all to
do with religion to be a great teacher.
>> Yes.
>> Correct.
>> And this is true of most of what you
would call or recognize as masters. Most
of them had no intention of creating a
religion.
Do you understand?
>> Yes.
>> It was about helping others recognize
that they are as powerful as the teacher
teaching that everyone is or at least
has the capacity and potential to be the
same to have the same understandings and
perspectives to elevate themselves. Yes.
>> Yes. that all can be masters, all can be
teachers.
>> Yes.
>> Therefore, the misinterpretation of this
and the idea that there needs to be
somebody in between you and your
connection to creation in order to
interpret that connection for you is
what religion is.
But with your own connection and knowing
that you are self-empowered that you are
in every way equal to the idea at least
potentially of any of the ascended
masters
then you don't necessarily need to
express that through the concept of
religion unless that's simply a
permission slip that works for you.
>> Got it.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes. And I've heard about permission
slips a lot. It's very
>> by the way.
>> Yes.
Mhm.
>> If it hadn't been for the fact
[clears throat] that an extraterrestrial
society referred to as the Anunnaki
hadn't used their genetic material
to create the idea of Homo sapien from
the natural hominid that evolved on your
planet and created Homo sapien at that
time to be someone who should look up to
them as superior. If that hadn't
happened, it is unlikely you would ever
have developed religion on your planet.
>> That was my next question.
>> Well, I've already answered it.
[laughter]
>> All right. So, in relation to the
potential of the future. Yes.
>> And I know probabilities and potentials
are always a part of the future. Yes.
Um, and I come from a place of
innovation in healthcare and I'm just
interested in some possibilities within
neuroscience, neurology, cancer,
genetics within the next 50 to 60 years
in terms of innovation.
>> Well, you are finding out more and more
that it's all about vibration. It's all
about resonance. It's all about states
of being. that if you can find the
vibrational equation that represents a
certain state of being and you can
impose that vibrational frequency on
something that is out of alignment with
that state of being in a specific way,
you can bring it back into alignment
with that state of being which will
cause a transformation to take place
within that thing.
>> Yes.
>> That's the basis
>> interesting
>> for all you're talking about. That's the
fundamental principle behind everything
that you just asked about.
>> So on a really pragmatic level, if
somebody's really sick with heart
failure or heart disease, how do they
get back into alignment?
>> Again, they can
depending upon the reason for the
creation of that experience because not
everyone will necessarily need or want
to be healed.
>> You follow me? because they may be
creating that experience for a very
specific reason that they need to go
through or that someone else close to
them needs to experience. So you have to
look at it first on a case by case
person by person basis as to why that's
happening.
But if there is within their choices the
probability of allowing them to heal
themselves,
then the idea can be that you need to
chart and measure what the natural
healed vibration of that particular
being would be or that particular organ
would be. And then imposing that
vibration in a specific way at a
specific frequency into that area can
either allow the tissue to regenerate
back to that vibrational state that
represents the healed state or at the
very least may cause certain
inspirations within you. If you need to
go through a process to create the
process that is necessary to bring that
organ back to a healed state by just
simply immersing in that vibration that
represents the healed state of that
organ.
>> Very cool. Thank you. Very interesting.
>> Does that help you?
>> That helps a lot. Yeah. Um
>> there is also a technique that was used
in Atlantean times that is kind of akin
to the concept of hypnosis because
in hypnosis you can actually be unlocked
from a particular reality idea and you
can be induced into another reality
idea.
More exploration on the concept of what
you now presently refer to as multiple
personality disorder
>> may be important here because there
already have been measurements of
different personalities having
completely different physical states.
Yes, one personality can actually have a
disease but when it shifts to the other
personality there's no sign of the
disease. Yes, there are case studies.
>> When you can really understand what's
going on there, you'll have your answer.
>> Yes.
>> Mhm.
>> Because they are actually, regardless of
whether it looks like it's the same
body, the same person, they are actually
two different people.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. That's
>> And there are always
>> alternate and parallel versions of
everyone. Yes. Yes.
>> Somewhere there must be a parallel
version of a person with a disease that
doesn't have it.
>> All right.
>> Finding that vibration and inducing them
to follow and match that frequency will
allow them to become that version of
themselves that not only doesn't have
the disease but never did because it's
not in their history, the new person
that they're becoming.
Yes.
Making sense?
>> Mhm. This is a way to use parallel
realities as a healing technique
and that to some degree is the future of
medicine.
>> Thanks.
>> You are welcome.
>> Appreciate it. [applause]
>> [sighs]
>> Hello, Bashar.
>> And to you, good day.
>> I have two questions.
>> Yes.
>> Al-Qaeda.
>> Boo Haram, Al-Shabaab, and the Islamic
State. Is there is there a message or a
commonality of and maybe just explain
kind of what's going on? We don't we
don't always get the right uh the news
stories or the right
>> there are several things
>> things
>> again in terms of the expression that
would be the negative side there is as
we have already been discussing a lot of
fear-based beliefs a lot of sense of
being attacked a lot of sense of
diminishment
a lot of sense of lack of
self-empowerment
so there is a lot of fear [snorts]
that reveals itself in the lack ashing
out that is done. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> Does that answer your question
sufficiently or is there something else
you wish to understand?
>> So there's fear on on the part of the
organizations like the Islamic State or
al-Shabaab.
>> Of course they
>> again as we have already explained the
greatest power requires the gentlest
touch. If anyone has to force an idea,
an ideology, a perspective on anyone
else, what they're saying is they don't
believe in the power of that idea.
Because if it really was a powerful
idea, why wouldn't everyone gravitate to
it? Because everyone wants to feel
powerful. Yes.
>> Yes. So if an idea is not being
gravitated to
yet someone believes that it should be
and forces others to do so they don't
believe in its power either.
Yes.
>> Right. Okay. Thank you. And the second
question is in your world
what kind of leaders or do you have
leaders and how are they chosen and what
is their role? No, no, no. As we have
described, we function on synchronism.
Pure synchronicity. Everyone is exactly
where they need to be, exactly when they
need to be there just by following their
highest passion. Now, there are
individuals who may choose themselves to
be organizers of sorts to help
facilitate an amplification of
synchronism in many ways to ensure that
things are running smoothly that way.
But they're not in that sense leaders.
We have no government in the way that
you choose to express that idea because
everything functions synchronistically.
We understand the mechanism of
synchronism and we use it and therefore
the leader if you want to call it that
is synchronism itself is the structure
of existence itself that we simply take
advantage of.
>> Yes.
>> Does that make sense to you?
>> Yes, it does.
>> Does that answer your question?
>> Yes. Was there something else?
>> Well, I wanted to ask a little bit about
the pyramids.
>> Which ones?
>> Since there are so many pyramids in in
Egypt and in Asia, is there is there
also a an error of when those were built
and for a certain like global meaning
when they were built?
>> The oldest ones, yes. Approximately
10,500
BC as you call it. and they had great
understanding of what they were doing.
Then the knowledge was lost over time
and a lot of the later pyramids do not
function in the same way that the
earlier ones did. The great pyramid of
Giza served many different kinds of
functions when it was operational in its
pristine state. Not the least of which
was that initiate priests when brought
into the understandings of the mysteries
of creation would be led into the king's
chamber and would lie down in the stone
coffer and they would be taught to
generate the gamma state in a meditation
and the stone coffer and the king's
chamber was designed to amplify and
magnify that gamma state to the point
where it reverberated and amplif
amplified and amplified and then
suddenly pop them out of their bodies so
that in astral form they could go to
higher realms, gain knowledge, bring it
back and share that knowledge with
society. Although of course the
priesthood usually kept those things to
themselves as to how they achieved that
knowledge. They would just simply dole
it out as they needed to.
>> You follow?
>> Does that answer your question? So could
could we do the same thing if we went
into the pyramid and
>> well yes to some degree although again
there has been some deterioration over
time so it's not really functioning at
peak performance
>> but yes it could be used as a permission
slip if you yourself
add to it
all the things that are missing in your
own energy field.
Does that make sense?
>> Yes. use your own energy field to add
the things that are now missing and you
could achieve the same effect. Yes. As a
permission slip. Of course, you don't
need the pyramid to do that necessarily.
>> Mhm.
>> But you can take advantage of that if
you wish. It's up to you.
>> Okay. Good.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
[applause]
Hey Bashar,
>> how are you? Good day.
>> So last session I had talked to you
about a dream that I had about
the reptilian human sexual contact.
>> Yes. So um elaborating more on that um
was that a actual experience that I was
having or yes
>> it um because I also got a connection
with my subconscious mind that it also
um was connecting me more deeply with my
subconscious mind bringing bringing
consciousness into the subconscious.
Well, bringing the subconscious into the
conscious.
>> Oh, yes. Bringing the subconscious into
the conscious.
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
>> Although you are also correct in the
other direction because many of you
think that the subconscious and
unconscious are lower than your physical
conscious mind. But they're not. They're
higher.
The physical mind is the lowest level.
The conscious mind is the lowest level.
>> Subconscious is above that. unconscious
is above that because you're going
toward the idea of the higher mind.
>> Yes.
>> Yes. So I also got the connection of the
reptilians and the Anunnaki. Um and I
was wondering if I got a inspiration
that there's an alternate timeline where
humans were created not to mine gold.
>> Yes. Of course.
Yes.
>> Anything you can imagine in general is
somewhere a reality. You can't imagine
non-existence.
>> Right? So we there's an alternate
timeline where we were not created to
look up to them. That we were created in
as equals
>> and that to some degree is where you're
shifting to.
>> Yes.
>> That is so exciting.
>> Yes, it is.
Um, also, um,
along the lines of the subconscious
mind, um, was the Sphinx Anabis at one
time?
>> Anubis.
>> Yes.
>> It was the jackal.
>> The jackal.
>> Not a lion. It was the jackal, the god
of the underworld,
>> right?
>> So to speak.
>> That's That's really awesome. Yay.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes. Uh, one more thing.
>> Yes.
>> Um, or actually two more. Does
Anubis and your father Anubis
>> Anubis does Anubis and your father do
they have similar energies?
>> They do.
Thank you for picking up on that.
>> Yeah.
I I I I actually thought maybe it was
your dad, but I just they resonated so
strongly.
>> Yes, there is an energetic connection.
It's not that Anubis is my father,
>> right?
>> But my father does have a very strong
connection to the archetypal level
consciousness that you know in your
reality as Anubis. Yes.
Um, yeah, with all the hybridization
going on, [laughter]
I mean, we it's just we have so much
inside of us that doesn't usually look
that doesn't represent our physicality.
>> Yes.
>> Um, so that's
>> there's a lot more going on in your
world than you are aware of.
>> Right. And then one more thing. Uh,
thank you. Um, my alternate incarnation
in Esasani,
>> one of them.
>> Thank you. Um,
is it at the same time that you're
there?
>> Partially. There's an overlap.
>> Hello. Yay. [laughter]
That's
>> all right. Hello. [laughter]
I mean hello in my alternate incarnation
and hello right now as of
>> um also I want to say hello to Cybo and
and tell him thank you because um as you
have he also has had a very positive
impact in my life and I want to thank
him for that and you.
>> All right. Well, thank you for creating
the positive impact in your own life.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> thank you. Thank you so much.
>> You are welcome so much.
[applause]
>> Hello Bashar.
>> How are you? Good day.
>> Happy birthday yesterday.
>> All right. Thank you.
>> What did you do?
>> Anything I wanted. [laughter]
>> Can
>> which I do every day anyway.
>> Okay.
Can we hang out for celebrate on your
birthday?
>> Can you what?
>> Hang out
>> party.
>> You can have whatever party you wish.
>> Okay.
Thank you.
>> I'm not stopping you.
>> Okay. With with you.
>> Well, not with me physically.
>> Okay.
All right. Um
>> but if you want to create a party, go
right ahead.
>> Okay.
Thank you.
>> And I have a question about my sleeping
habit.
>> Your sleeping habits.
>> Mhm.
>> As opposed to your natural cycle.
>> My natural cycle is
too opposite from the social.
So very opposite like
>> so what?
>> Why aren't you following your natural
sleep cycle?
>> Okay. Natural sleep cycle is most times
2 2 to 5:00 a.m. 6:00 a.m. I'm very
waking up.
>> Yes. Well, if you follow your excitement
and express the things that are
representative of your excitement,
>> they will most likely fall into your
natural sleep cycle instead of forcing
yourself to do things that are not
necessarily representative of your
excitement that force you to have an
unnatural sleep cycle.
>> Okay? Do you understand? It's up to you,
>> right?
>> But it's
>> more harmonious to follow your natural
cycle and do the things in your life
that would then fall into place in your
natural cycle.
>> Like it's
like it's not it's not really bother
like used to be. But still sometimes
when I think about, oh, I couldn't make
this. I couldn't make this because I
don't like waking up in the morning. I
don't I don't know. Like,
>> you're just creating excuses.
>> Mhm.
>> Are you acting on your highest
excitement every moment that you
possibly can? Yes or no?
>> Yes.
>> You are. Are you sure?
>> Doesn't sound like it because you just
said you were not following your natural
sleep cycle. Wouldn't that be more
exciting
>> to be able to follow your natural cycle?
>> Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> Then when I asked you if you're
following your excitement and you said
yes, you were fibbing.
>> Okay.
>> So stop fibbing
>> and follow your excitement. Part of
which is your natural sleep cycle. And
when you do that,
>> things may come to you in that cycle
that will be representative of things
you can do that will fall into that
natural cycle.
>> You don't have to force yourself to do
things
>> and have a sleep cycle that is not
natural for you because that will make
you tired.
>> Like
>> it will exhaust you.
>> It will not really refresh you. Mhm.
>> You may be able to endure it for a
while,
but it won't really energize you.
Following your natural cycle will
energize you and will bring you
synchronistically the things that you
can do that will fit the cycle.
Remember, you can't experience what
you're not the vibration of first.
So you have to be natural first in order
for synchronicity to present to you
opportunities that would fit within the
natural cycle. Otherwise you can't see
them there would be invisible to you
those opportunities.
>> Do you understand?
>> Yes. Very like totally. Thank you. And
>> yes,
>> and you told us fair tax because it's
close from Oakland. How about in Japan
and Las Vegas?
>> Well, that's up to the people in the
area. Now, your Las Vegas is still part
of your United States, which is
exploring the idea of the fair tax.
>> Japan obviously is a different culture,
>> but you can create something similar if
you wish.
>> It's up to you. We're simply saying that
that at the moment
>> is the most aligned representation for
what it is based on the economic
structure you have for what it is that
would best avail the health of the
economic structure. We're not saying
that this is the ideal scenario.
Ultimately you will go through many
different transitions with regard to the
economics of your world and you'll have
many different ways of expressing that
idea. The idea simply right now is that
as you have designed your economic
structure, the fair tax is the one that
is most aligned for the growth and
natural health of that economic
structure at this moment.
>> Okay.
>> Does that help?
>> Yes.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you. I have one more question.
>> I beg your pardon.
>> I have one more question.
>> Yes. I had a dream two two weeks ago
about
um Mount Chester.
>> Yes.
>> And I was I was to remember how he looks
like
white skin, brown hair, and a little
ugly face.
And like right after I woke up, I
realized he was he was like gatekeeper
for Mount Chester.
>> In some senses, yes. Although that's a
slight interpretation in human terms,
but nevertheless, is that some place
you're attracted to go and explore?
>> Yes.
>> When will you go?
>> Um, this Sunday night.
>> Oh, all right. Have a good time.
>> Okay.
>> And pleasant dreams.
>> Thank you.
>> [applause]
>> Hi Bashar
>> and you good day.
>> I have a question to you about um doing
and being and over the last 5 years I've
been trying to make a transition
from my career that I've created for
myself. Um I went into nursing school.
>> Yes. and found out that the current
situation of nursing is not with what
I'm aligned with.
>> All right. What are you aligned with?
>> Well, that's what I've been pursuing in
>> pursuing
>> in my education. I wanted to take
advantage of my RN by teaching people
how to
uh take care of their bodies through
nutrition and lifestyle choices.
>> And that's exciting for you.
>> It's exceptionally exciting for me.
>> All right. So, that's what you're doing.
Yes. Yes. My question though has to do
with doing and being.
>> What's the difference?
>> Because I am
>> What's the difference in your
definition?
>> Doing is like you got to do do. I've got
this this list of tasks that I have to
complete in order to um accomplish what
it is I'm wanting. and being
>> is feels more in alignment with what
you're talking about in terms of
>> if you are in [clears throat] the state
of being
that is appropriate for you, harmonious
and in alignment with your true
frequency.
The things that you need to do
will also align with your state of being
and will not need or require effort so
much as you will simply take the natural
actions that are the natural flowing
result of being in that state. So it
won't necessarily have to be a list of
tasks that you have to do d do.
There may be some of them but remember
that synchronicity is the organizing
principle. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> And if it is the organizing principle
which it is then by acting on your
excitement
the things that come with the highest
excitement in whatever order that they
come are the things that need doing. But
you will do them from a state of being
that allows them to also be exciting
actions.
And it will not be more than you need to
do. It will regulate itself in order, in
timing, in everything in such a way as
to show you exactly what needs to be
done and when. And no more than that
will be needed.
Does this help?
Are you understanding this concept?
>> It does. I
>> Yeah,
>> it's in translating it in my life has
been the challenge because I've been
applying what you talk about, I'd say.
>> But you're not that's the point. You're
not not quite.
You're still allowing outdated
definitions to create a sense
within you that more needs to be done
than may need to be done. You're not
letting synchronicity show you what
needs to be done. You're making an
assumption of what you need to do. Yes.
>> I guess so.
>> You guess or you know so
>> it's just I feel like I'm doing okay.
So, I don't I'm not getting paid.
>> Let's take it to a specific level
>> to help illustrate the point.
>> Can you describe the idea now? You're
doing what excites you. Yes.
>> Mhm.
>> Can you describe the idea of this list
of tasks and how you create that?
>> Okay. I'm working with Okay. I have
three people that I work with.
>> Yes.
>> And that when I work with them, it
really elicits that feeling of
excitement. I love it. They're making
changes. We all are really excited
>> and so
>> okay so where does
>> there's this on this side over here and
then there's what I've been doing for
work over here and I'm trying to make
the leap of see these people aren't
paying me I'm doing it to elicit that
feeling of excitement but I haven't
>> like to get out and to market what I'm
doing requires time so there's more
things that I have to do
>> so what why isn't that part of your
excitement
>> because it's one more thing that I have
to do with all that. See, I'm
>> one more thing. If you were doing it in
the way that is exciting for you, it
would be one more thing you wouldn't be
able to wait to do. You're not doing it
in alignment with excitement. That's
what we're saying. You're making those
things look like tasks, defining them as
something other than your excitement. If
those things actually need to be done,
there is a way to do them that is part
and parcel of your excitement and you're
not doing them that way. That's why they
feel like they don't belong. That's why
they feel like tasks because you're
using old definitions about the way
you're going about doing those things or
think that you have to go about doing
those things and making them non-exiting
>> when you could be inventing ways to do
the things that need to be done in more
exciting ways by using your imagination
and not just assuming there's only one
way to do these things to get the word
out to market yourself.
You're limiting your imagination with
these definitions that limit you.
>> Yes.
>> Can we use your imagination to come up
with something as you would say in your
language out of the box to advertise and
market yourself in a way that would be
more exciting for you? Will you allow
your imagination the free reign to do
that or are you going to keep it in a
box?
>> I will take it out of the box.
>> All right. So now open up your
imagination and now comes the idea of
I'm excited to market myself to get the
word out that I'm doing this. That is
exciting. Yes, just getting the word
out. Is that exciting?
>> Relating to people is exciting to me and
then it naturally flows from me when I
do that. So yes, that is exciting.
>> So first question, why isn't that
enough?
because I'm still compressing my vision
around that I've got to work this amount
of hours per week to make enough money
and then when I get home I'm dead tired
and I'm like
>> then why don't you charge more?
>> I have been I've jumped up my rates a
lot.
>> Do you feel good or bad about doing
that?
>> I feel fine about it, but I kind of feel
like I've reached the ceiling for what
I'm doing and now I'm trying to make the
leap over to what I'm wanting to be
truly doing. But you keep going back and
forth here.
>> Keep going back and forth between two
different completely different ideas.
>> I know that's what I'm living is two
completely different ideas.
>> But stop.
>> That's what we're saying. Why aren't you
just living your excitement? Don't you
believe it can support you?
>> I do, but it's like no no no no
no. You're already in trouble.
[laughter]
[snorts] When that question is asked,
anything other than yes is a no. So I do
but
>> means no.
>> Do you understand? Because if you really
knew that it would support you, you
would simply say yes, I know that you
would know it. So here's the crux.
Here's the issue. You don't know that it
can support you. You're not sure. You
don't believe it.
That's where you need to focus.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> What are you afraid of? Why don't you
believe that what really excites you can
support you?
>> Because of the complexity of
relationship and talking about money and
how is bringing that into
the dynamics of a relationship and
saying I mean
>> what are you saying? Is this another way
of saying that you don't like to charge
for your services?
>> No. No, no, no.
>> What are you saying?
>> I'm saying that
I have to make I'm making money to
support my family and myself.
>> I understand. And you do understand that
the definition of abundance is wider
than just money. Yes.
>> Yes, I do. [clears throat]
>> Are you sure?
>> I'm Yes.
>> All right. So why don't you believe that
what excites you can support you in the
way you need to be supported to continue
to act on your excitement? Because
that's one of the tools in the kit, you
know.
>> Yeah.
>> That it supports you to allow you to
continue to do your excitement in
whatever way you need to be supported.
Not the way you may think you need to be
supported in the way you need to be
supported.
>> Yes.
>> Big difference.
So,
are you afraid that your excitement
can't support you? Yes or no?
Hesitation.
>> No. No. No. It's just like this. It's
like jumping off a cliff.
>> Exactly. And I would encourage you not
to do so if you don't know that you have
a parachute.
So, what you're saying is you're holding
on to old beliefs that you believe you
need, old things that you believe you
need for support. And that's fine
as long as you are at least allowing
yourself to do the things that excite
you to some degree. It can over time
demonstrate to you, prove to you that it
can support you. The question is, how
long are you willing to wait?
I'm well my goal is to start at the
beginning of the year. I kind of feel
like the end of the year.
>> But are you afraid to?
>> I'm excited and afraid. I mean I am
excited.
>> Which is it?
>> I'm Yes.
>> They're not the same thing.
>> It's there's a They're mixed. They're
together.
>> No, you go back and forth is what you're
like a little pingpong ball.
>> Exactly.
>> So you are excited sometimes. you were
afraid other times. So in the meantime,
use that process. Find the things that
you're afraid of. Find the beliefs that
generate the fear. Identify them. Let
them go. That's your task right now.
[snorts]
So that when you clear yourself out, you
will just be excited and you will know
it can support you.
>> Yes.
>> Does that help?
>> It helps tremendously.
>> Are you a little bit more excited now?
>> I'm a lot more excited. Oh, all right.
Thank you.
>> Thank you.
[applause]
>> Hello, Taba.
>> Nia, is it time for Cosmic News Network?
>> It is.
[clears throat]
>> Okay, back to the election now.
>> Not yet.
>> What time is it?
>> Uh, I think we have about 10 minutes.
>> I didn't ask you that, did I?
>> I'm not going to tell you.
>> Oh, all [laughter] right.
This is Cosmic News Network signing off.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no.
>> What time is it?
>> No, cuz some people ask questions and we
weren't
>> What time is it?
>> 3:30. Can we have 10 minutes?
>> Thank you for asking.
>> I did.
>> Did you?
>> No, you told me.
>> No, no, no, no, no. [laughter]
>> Somebody help me here.
I don't want to get into trouble with
you.
>> Too late.
[laughter]
>> Please proceed. [clears throat]
>> Okay. Um, Trump appears to be a bit
dumbfounded by having his bluff called.
Is that
>> Well, it's very rare that someone is
smartfounded.
[laughter]
>> So, is there a chance that the
seriousness of this sinks in and makes
him a better person?
>> There's a chance.
>> What are the odds?
even
>> because of that narcissistic
narcissistic.
>> It's too soon to tell.
>> It's still too fresh.
Remember that you're not the only ones
in shock.
>> Yeah, he's in shock, too. Right.
[clears throat] With the new president,
do we have a better chance of avoiding
the economic collapse that was predicted
or the major economic
devaluation? You do have better odds in
certain ways. Yes.
>> And the risk of a terrorist incident
>> still pending,
but we'll see. There are moves that need
to be made first that will tell us more
that have to do, as you already know,
with Jerusalem.
>> Yes. In fact, Trump said that they were
talking about moving the capital of
Israel to Jerusalem.
>> Yes. And that will start something
moving,
but we'll see. There are other pathways
through it other than a terrorist
attack, but we'll see. It's too soon to
tell.
Um, one person wanted to know if the
shift to the parallel earth will contain
any republicans
[laughter]
in the sense that there will be an
[clears throat] interim period where it
will be more representative of the
original republic
then yes, but not in the way that they
exist now. So as the parallel realities
get farther and farther apart, will
literally you stop seeing at some point
the people who are of opposing
viewpoints?
>> Yes, eventually.
>> But that's not like for a long time,
right?
>> Long is relative. Some people may see it
in their lifetime. Others may see it in
a generation or two.
Depends on how they're looking.
Depends on their perspective. depends on
their process. Depends on how long they
may need something of opposition to hang
around as a reflection. Depends.
This one's a really cool one. This one
says, "The first day Trump takes office
is January 21, 2017, and Trump will be
70 years old. 7 months and 7 days that
day."
>> There you go.
>> What does that tell you? Lucky seven.
that it's not an accident.
>> Um, and with all these protests, what
are some of the benefits of all the
protests that are happening?
>> Well, again, certainly you can see that
there are different reality perspectives
here. Now, of course, the lashing out is
not necessarily constructive, but the
protest demonstrates in general that
there are truly different realities
here. You're beginning to recognize that
it's actually being shown to you that
there are different realities side by
side.
>> Is there any chance that the electorate
college will not support Trump?
>> Not much of a chance that it will not,
but
you may find that within about 15 to 20
of your years, there will no longer be
an electoral college. That's got a
higher probability.
>> Yeah, there definitely were some people
who wanted to know that. Um will
let's see
um what if Donald Donald Trump
implements unjust laws like
discrimination and things like that?
What is the appropriate way to respond
to things like that?
>> Compassion.
>> And does that mean that you should break
the law or should you follow that law or
how does that work?
>> We cannot advise you on that.
>> Right? because we never advise you to
break a law. But we understand the idea
that sometimes what you would call a
quote unquote just rebellion may require
it. But we cannot be engaged in your
politics to that degree to advise you on
that one way or the other.
Okay. And then lastly, um, what
percentage of Earth's population
contributed genetically to the
hybridization program?
>> About 15%.
>> And so, of the people in this room, what
percentage of these people are involved
in the hybridization program?
>> About 75%.
And um do you know what happened to
Napoleon when he was inside the great
pyramid in Egypt?
>> He had a vision.
>> Do you know what his vision was?
>> He actually had the vision of his defeat
>> and sought to see if it could be
changed.
>> No. because he stumbled into a vibration
that represented a parallel timeline. He
understood there were other options but
did not really understand the amount of
momentum that was behind the timeline he
would already established for himself.
>> That's interesting. Okay. And lastly,
for those of us who are joining us in
Europe and are quite concerned about
what's happening in Europe, that
there's, you know, there's a lot of
antagonism around the refugees coming
into their country and that it seems
like the immigration issue is a big one
here too.
>> Yes. And so they were wondering what you
could share with us about this mirror
reflection that's happening in both
locations and what is the best way to
approach the whole situation
>> at this time. That is a subject that we
would need to spend more time on and we
will not address it at present.
>> Okay. So but in terms of the people in
Europe feel staying calm I guess with
all the change.
>> Absolutely. It's the same ideas that
we've had here.
>> Yes.
>> Which is that you find a positive way to
>> find the path through it. Now that all
bets are off, you have the opportunity
to start crystallizing a reality of your
preference in a variety of ways by
acting on your passion. Because now
everything is unlocked.
Now you don't have to rely on what's
expected. The unexpected has now reared
its head so strongly that you are truly
unlocked from the idea of any
expectation other than those that are
truly relevant. So allow yourself to
take advantage of this limbo state by
understanding there is very little now
restricting you from crystallizing the
reality that you prefer.
>> Okay. Well, thank you. Thank you for
that update from the Cosmic News
Network. It is our pleasure.
>> And
since you're in charge, what would you
like to do now? [laughter]
>> We would be very excited for all of you
to take a short break [laughter] and
then we will resume the transmission
with your holotope experience.
>> Okay.
[applause]
>> Hello, Bashar.
>> And are you good day? What is your
story?
>> My name's Kelly. I'm 22.
>> Oh, all right. That's part of your
story.
>> Yes. All right. This is a story about
Kelly 22.
And what is Kelly's story?
>> It's a very emotional story.
What is it emotional about?
Take your time.
What are you feeling?
>> What was that?
>> What are you feeling?
>> It's It's overwhelming. It's really
exciting that
>> Are you feeling love within yourself?
>> Yes.
>> All right.
>> And I'm starting to realize
>> that you deserve it.
>> Yes.
>> Oh, all right. That's a nice story.
>> For a long time, I felt empty and and
sad. And
>> Yes. You told yourself a very empty
story for a long time, but now you are
telling a very fulfilling story.
>> Yes. And um
>> Yes.
>> Part of it is
as I'm growing and I'm starting to learn
a lot.
>> Yes.
>> Um
>> which is what growing is all about.
>> Yes. Um,
a lot [snorts] of a lot of it is
memories that I'm trying to
>> not trying
>> that I'm that I'm remembering.
>> Yes. [snorts]
>> And I just
>> that have to do with what?
>> With myself as a young girl.
>> Yes.
>> Because I feel a lot of this a lot of
things I blocked out and I started to
forget [clears throat] who I was and
>> All right.
>> Because it was painful to think about
it.
>> All right. But now you understand that
you can invent yourself at every moment
as a new person. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> And as you do so, the things that you're
calling past memories actually have no
longer any relevance for you because
you're not that person anymore.
Literally,
they literally have nothing to do with
you anymore if you choose to define
yourself that way. Do you understand
this concept?
>> Yes, but sure.
>> All right. And um every day I I I I um I
remember I I I spend time by myself
remembering myself as a child now that
I'm trying to now that I'm accepting
and and trying to get rid of those
blocks. And one of them
>> It's not about trying to get rid of the
blocks. It's about investigating the
belief systems that you've bought into
and identifying those beliefs so that
you can recognize that the beliefs that
are out of alignment with your truth
don't belong to you and you can let them
go. You may have simply been given them
by parents, by friends, by society, but
once you identify them as someone else's
beliefs, you will understand they don't
belong to you and you can let them go
because you don't want to carry what
doesn't belong to you. You understand?
>> Yes.
>> So let them go if they don't belong to
you. Because once you understand they
don't belong to you, they have no more
effect on you. Because effect is only
what you choose to be affected by. And
if you have beliefs that are
unconscious, you feel the effect because
you're not aware of what the belief is.
But once you know what the belief is,
once you identify it, it no longer has
an effect because you can recognize you
no longer prefer it to have an effect.
you're no longer choosing it to have an
effect and so it no longer does.
Identification of the beliefs is key.
Thank you. And one more is as I'm
remembering these um memories of myself
as a kid. A lot of them they they are
exciting and and and I feel really happy
when I think about it. But then in the
end I feel at the end of of that
realization I I feel sad because it's
gone and I
>> because it's what?
>> You feel sad because it's what
it
>> it's not gone. I [laughter] know it
>> it will never go away.
Remember that growth is the process of
inclusion not exclusion.
You will always be aware of that as a
possible experience. But you can
understand you don't have to choose to
buy into that experience as having
anything to do with the you you're
defining yourself to be now.
Do you understand the difference?
>> Yes. If you truly are a different
person, if you truly define yourself as
a new person, then linearly speaking
from a space-time perspective, if you
truly have defined yourself as a new
person, then wouldn't you as a new
person have a different past than the
person that was there a moment ago?
>> Could you repeat that one more time?
>> Yes, I can. And for the first time,
if you truly understand that you're
defining yourself as a new person and
understand clearly that when you do
redefine yourself as a new person, that
this is not just a metaphorical idea
that you literally literally literally
are a new person. Then linearly speaking
from your space-time perspective, every
different person has a different
history. So if you really are defining
yourself as a different person than you
used to be, then you have a different
past. You have a different childhood.
Define the childhood that belongs to the
person you're defining yourself to be.
Now, as a young adult, you can define
the childhood. Now, you create the past
from the present, not the other way
around. The past does not define the
present unless you choose to create that
illusion. But you're creating that
illusion from the present because you
only exist in the present. So any
so-called past that you're remembering,
you're actually creating the
relationship to that idea now from the
person you're defining yourself to be.
So if you define yourself differently,
you can actually know you've created a
different past, a different
relationship. So define the child you'd
prefer to be or in your language define
the childhood you would prefer to have
had that is relevant for the person
you're defining yourself to be now and
recognize that the so-called memories of
the childhood you don't prefer belong to
another woman.
They don't belong to you. It's her
childhood, not yours.
Not yours. literally not yours. It's not
about ignoring it. It's not about
covering it up. It's about acknowledging
it as the stepping stone that you were
able to use to define who it is you
prefer to be. And in so doing, the
childhood she had helped you become the
person you are that has a different
childhood.
That's the paradox.
Is this making sense?
>> Yes. So you, whoever you are now, never
had that childhood, even though you can
still be aware of those so-called
memories, but those so-called
experiences belong to her, not you.
She's in another reality now. You're not
her any longer. Literally, literally,
literally. I don't care what you think.
You still look like in the mirror.
That's just an illusion of continuity.
You're actually a different person,
literally, because person is an
artificial construct. Personality is
just composed of beliefs and emotions
and thoughts and behaviors. It's a mask
that the consciousness wears to have a
physical experience. It's just part of
the ego structure mask. Personality,
when you change anything about your
beliefs or your feelings or your
behaviors or your thoughts, you actually
change the person literally that you
are. Even though you think you look the
same, you're actually not the same
person. You just look similar to her.
That's all similar because you're
creating the sense of similarity. But in
fact, as many people on your planet have
already experienced, when you change
yourself enough, when you know you've
changed yourself enough, you can
actually look so different because you
really are a different person that some
of your quote unquote friends may
actually not recognize you. Who are you?
Oh, I didn't recognize. Why do you look
so different? Because I am [laughter]
I am a different person. Now you have
maintained a connection with those
people in a manner in a manner. You've
co-created a reality together with those
friends so that you're interacting with
a version in your reality, a version of
those friends that contains the ability
to recognize the difference. Were you to
simply not need that experience,
then you would simply be capable of
changing enough. I'm just talking about
a possibility here. You would be capable
of changing your appearance to match the
differences within you enough so that
any of the people that the old person
used to call friends would actually
literally not recognize you when you
walked by and wouldn't even say you look
different. They just wouldn't know who
you were. But you don't necessarily want
to create that much detachment. So you
maintain the idea of the version of them
that will recognize the difference but
will also show you that you really have
changed. You can use the friends as a
reflective mirror in that way to prove
to yourself you really are a different
person by having them reflect to you
that they almost didn't recognize you.
>> Yes.
>> You understand?
>> But you really are a different person.
Literally. Take me literally. This is
not a metaphor.
>> Yes.
>> It's not an analogy. Everything you
change every time you change changes
everything. Literally. You are in an
entirely different parallel reality as
an entirely different person if that's
how you choose to define yourself to be.
And you can know that whoever was here a
moment ago, whoever she was, wish her
well, bless her, give her unconditional
love, but those memories of childhood
are hers. They're not yours.
>> Does that help you?
>> Yes. And [clears throat] um one more
thing.
>> Yes.
>> Part of um my story and in my dream
state,
>> yes,
>> I have
a reoccurring dream.
>> Yes. How exciting.
And
>> do share.
>> I
>> Yes. Do you need a hug?
>> I'm at the I'm at the ocean and
>> Do you need a hug?
>> Yes. [laughter] No, I don't.
>> Somebody give her a hug.
>> No, there is nothing to apologize for.
This is the process of discovering your
beliefs.
YOU SEE, you have been bold enough, bold
enough and strong enough to choose an
event, an experience called experiencing
a lot of emotionality so that I may
recognize through these emotions what I
believe to be true. Very bold, very
strong, very exciting story. [laughter]
I'm on the edge of my seat
and so is the channel's body.
>> Okay, thank you. And so this reoccurring
story is what?
>> I'm I'm I'm at the I'm at the beach and
I I get I see this tidal wave.
>> Yes.
>> And it's coming.
>> I usually I I
>> I It varies. Sometimes I feel really
scared and I paralyze, but then the wave
lands on me.
>> Yes.
>> And um I just float with it like I feel
like I'm going to get hurt or something.
And
>> and but I just I go along into the wave.
>> And what happened then?
>> And then I wake up. [laughter]
>> And then what happened?
>> Don't you hear that a lot in stories?
And then what happened?
>> Yes.
>> How exciting.
>> And you understand the symbology
archetypally for yourself?
>> That's what I'm trying to understand
because
>> water represents emotion. You said
you're overwhelmed by your emotional
feelings. The tidal wave. But if you go
with the flow, you're all right.
Your emotions can't smash you if you go
with the flow.
You won't be overwhelmed if you go with
the flow. You'll be fine.
>> Thank you.
>> That's the story of the title wave.
>> Does that help you?
>> Yes.
>> Then pleasant dreams to you in your new
story.
>> Thank you, BUSHER.
[applause]
>> My my what a loud story.
Hey Bashar and YOU GOOD DAY. WHAT IS
your story?
>> First I have a story of gratitude to you
and your family.
>> Our story of gratitude to you as well.
>> Thank you. Um in my story
I know I've chosen the theme of soul
awakening.
>> Well that's true of many of you
actually.
>> Yeah. Well
>> but your version of it is your story.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Congratulations.
>> Other versions are here.
>> Yes. Congratulations on such an exciting
story choice. Soul awakening.
>> Um,
>> how does it go? How does this story go
for you?
>> Well, I'm still expressing gratitude.
It's still a story of gratitude.
>> Oh. All right. Thank you.
>> Defining within myself cuz I know you
are within myself.
>> Yes.
>> A great mentor and a true friend
>> as you are to us. Remember, you're
mentors to us as well.
>> Yes.
And so
>> I've also attracted myself in this
story.
>> Yes.
>> To information about whom we on this
earth call masters.
>> Yes.
>> Um not masters of limitation. Well,
yeah. They would be masters of
limitation cuz they have mastered
themselves and limitation.
>> All right.
>> Um they talk about Neptune. And
>> are you referring to the idea of the
planet in your system or the archetypal
god form? Well, I'm not exactly sure,
but they say Neptune.
>> Yes.
>> Taking this on as much as I understand
it.
>> Yes. Um, they talk about a civilization
who composes the root race to humanity
and whose teachings they now live by.
All right. But you understand there are
no other indigenous physical life forms
such as your civilization physically on
any planets in your system.
>> They are talking about the idea of the
connection of non-physical consciousness
beings to different archetypal planets
in your system. Right?
>> Because the resonant vibration of those
beings simply matches the resonant
vibration of those planets as you have
laid your system out archetypally.
>> Right?
>> All right.
>> So,
>> so they identify with them in that way.
>> Right.
>> All right. And so,
>> and our teachings.
>> All right. And so, how does that
archetypal story serve you? Why have you
attracted yourself to this?
>> Because I want to live that story
>> which is in a nutshell means 25 words or
less. Pitch it to us. [laughter]
>> [clears throat]
>> That's the story of mastery over self,
mastery over limitation
to become a being who also projects and
represents the world's spirit. It is not
mastery over self is mastery of self.
>> Oh, right, right, right. Because it
includes, right?
>> Yes.
>> And you don't lose yourself. You will
always be what you consider to be you.
No matter how high you go.
>> No, no. I had no intention to convey the
thought that I would lose myself because
I must retain my essence.
>> We are just more clearly delineating the
definition that goes with the idea
called mastery over self. That implies
within the definition that you lose the
self. That's why mastery of self is more
of an appropriate way to define it
because then it's all inclusive and you
don't lose the selfidentity.
>> This and that.
>> Yes. This and that. Not this or that.
>> Okay. Um
as far as
the identifying with those teachings.
>> Yes.
>> And I I know I can use my own
synchronicity to attract them. But
>> Well, you always do. Yes.
And so could you throw me a bone?
[laughter]
>> A thigh bone? An arm bone? What kind of
a bone?
>> A bone of information
>> about what?
>> About these teachings,
>> but you haven't shared your story about
it yet. How does it resonate for you?
So that we can throw you the bone that
resonates to your particular
interpretation of the story.
>> Mhm.
Put it out there and you'll get
something back.
>> Well, I'm living my story.
>> Pitch us the story that attracts you.
Why are you attracted to this particular
resonant story?
>> Because it represents
Yes.
>> my ultimate beauty as a being
experiencing physical reality.
>> But what are the specifics of this story
that do that for you?
What are you specifically resonating to
in terms of the structure of this story?
What are the elements in the story?
>> To become a being that expresses
compassion and is removed from
suffering.
>> Removed.
You mean you're not choosing to suffer?
>> Right.
>> All right. Well, then don't choose to
suffer
>> anyway. Do you want the story to be more
complicated than that?
>> No. All right. Well, I've just thrown
you a bone.
Don't choose to suffer.
Don't choose to identify any experience
you have as suffering
and you won't experience it that way.
Can it be that simple?
>> Of course.
>> Does that help you?
>> Yes.
>> Does that answer your question?
>> Well, I wanted to know if there are any
physicalized
information
about these teachings that they have
represented in the story. Are you
looking for a permission slip? Yeah.
>> A physical permission slip?
>> Well, hasn't your imagination come up
with something that's a physicalized
representation of these teachings?
>> Not that I have currently.
>> Well, why don't you use your imagination
to do so if that's what you want? Maybe
you don't need one.
>> Are you talking about the idea of
creating them? If you want to create a
physicalized version or a physicalized
representation of this particular
permission slip of energy, you have the
imagination to do so. If you haven't
invented what you're asking for, maybe
you don't really believe you need it.
>> Well, I imagine them to be in some
sacred temple in the far east.
>> Oh, all right.
>> Written on manuscripts.
>> Um, then why not join them and write
your own manuscript
and that will be your permission slip?
>> Yes,
>> of course. Well, that was easy. Yes,
>> it's always easy.
>> Yes.
There you go.
>> So, write your story out in manuscript
form if that's what it takes to
represent that energy for you. If that's
what it takes to resonate within your
story, join them in what you imagine
they're doing archetypally and become
one of them and do what they do.
Remember that by mirroring
mirroring what you imagine is
representative of that reality, you will
then be expressing through physical
action the vibrations of that reality.
You will be a being in that reality and
thus then the things that are gerine to
that reality germanine to that reality.
>> Can you define that a little gerine? I
don't really understand that
relevant.
>> All right.
>> But there was another connotation that
you may discover later. Yeah, cuz I
noticed you break broke it down in a
very
>> Yes, I did. particular way. But that's
going to be one of those funny little
clues in your story that you're going to
have to become a detective to discover.
>> A detection story. I love that.
>> All right. So, go to your temple, write
your manuscript, become a detective. You
will see.
>> Yes. And I am doing my best to
>> I know.
>> All right.
>> That's all you need to do.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you,
>> teacher. We love you. our unconditional
love to you as well. [applause]
>> Good day.
>> Good day to you. I don't speak English
very well.
>> Neither do I.
>> Okay.
>> I come from Brazil and I live in
Barcelona.
>> All right. And um all my life
um work with spiritually but my channel
don't um align correctly.
>> What do you mean?
>> Because I don't uh my channel my being
don't speak the language the the people
understand.
>> It doesn't have to. The idea is I'm not
speaking any language at all. I'm
sending thoughts through a person that
is programmed with a language. So, it's
only going to come through a person in
the language that person is programmed
with unless
something about their belief system will
allow them to
override
their education and allow another
language to come through. But that's
rare and most often doesn't need to
happen because there are more than
enough people who speak certain
languages that entities can use as
translation devices without necessarily
having to force someone to speak a
different language they're not
programmed with.
>> Yes.
>> Do you understand?
>> No. But my son translate to me h uh how
I
uh al my energy my frequenc
align my energy
to the same frequency of my being the I
channel
>> by acting on your highest passion to the
best you are able with no insistence on
a particular outcome and letting
synchronicity guide you through life to
do the things you need to do to practice
more.
You will get better over time.
>> Practic more um
>> practice more
>> practice. Okay. Thank you Bashar very
much.
>> You are welcome.
[applause]
Hello. Um, good morning Bashar
>> and to you. Good day.
>> This is very exciting for me to be able
to talk to you.
>> It is exciting for us as well.
>> Um, I'm here with my best friends Nesh
and Rex today. And, uh, a question that
we commonly have is that we'll meet on a
weekend or an evening or an event like
this. We'll talk about your concepts
that you shared with us over YouTube.
>> Yes.
>> And we'll feel quite uplifted. Then
we'll go back into work mode on a
Monday, a Tuesday or Wednesday and we
find that our energy gets sucked out of
us.
>> Why do you choose that? Why not stay in
the state that you prefer?
>> We try.
>> No,
the idea isn't to try. The idea is to
choose what you prefer. What's so
difficult about choosing it? Are you
buying into belief systems that have
nothing to do with what you prefer? The
answer would be yes.
>> Yeah.
>> But why?
Why not find the beliefs that say that
you must buy into those beliefs?
>> True.
>> Well, why not?
Why not use the time to do that? Find
out what the beliefs are that would make
it seem logical in order for you to
choose things you don't prefer.
You must have beliefs attached in a way
that makes it seem to be the logical
thing to do. Find those beliefs and see
how nonsensical they are by identifying
them consciously. Once you identify them
consciously, if they're out of alignment
with what you prefer, they will appear
to be nonsensical. And as soon as they
appear nonsensical, they're gone.
The belief appearing nonsensical is not
the beginning of the process of letting
it go. It's the end of the process of
letting it go. But you have to find them
and allow them to appear nonsensical.
But right now, apparently if you keep
choosing them, they make sense to you
somehow to keep choosing things you
don't prefer. Only a negative belief can
make that possible. So find that
negative belief that makes the things
you don't prefer seem to be the logical
thing to do and you will see that it
makes no sense and then you will let it
go. Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Because it's a choice. It's always a
choice. You can't really anymore get
away with saying it's a tendency. It's a
habit. It's a pattern. Because if you
know it's a habit, it's not a habit. It
>> is a choice.
>> A habit is something you do that you
don't know you're doing. If you know
you're doing it, it's a choice. But that
gives you the power to change it,
knowing that it's a choice. Find out
what the belief is that makes it seem
like the logical choice to do something
you don't prefer. When you find out what
it is and let it go, making that choice
won't seem logical anymore. You'll make
different choices.
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Does that make sense?
>> It does.
>> Are you willing to allow it to be that
easy?
>> I am.
>> All right. Then have fun.
>> Thank you. Um
>> and fun on Tuesday and Wednesday and
Thursday and FRIDAY
and
Oh. Oh, it's Tuesday now.
>> Oh, it's Wednesday. That's even worse.
It's up to you.
Um I think that's a on a spectrum of
what can happen in a week. Um there's
lots of people out there who who need
love and need support. Yes. And um
another thing that we discussed is how
do you how do we help people?
>> By being yourself. How can you help
someone if you're not you?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> You have to be yourself in order to
actually be of assistance and service
and support to others. If you're not
supporting yourself, if you're not who
you really are, you can't be of any help
to anyone because you're not you.
Make sense? Yeah.
>> So just be the example by being yourself
and then you will know what to do. And
by the way, everyone is always
supported. You are never not supported.
It's just a matter of whether you are
supported in your negative beliefs or
whether you are supported in your
positive ones because creation won't
contradict you. If you buy into a
negative belief and you believe that
that's true for you, creation's going to
say, "Okay, I will unconditionally
support you in buying into that negative
belief." But if you change your mind and
make a different choice and say, "Now I
prefer to buy into the positive belief."
Creation will also say, "Okay, I now
support you in your positive belief." It
doesn't care what you choose because you
have free will. It will support you
unconditionally.
So the power, the freedom to choose is
in your hands. Creation will never
contradict you when you make a choice.
It will only support you in the choice
you've made, positive or negative.
Make sense?
>> Yes, it does.
>> Does this help you?
>> It does. Thank you.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you for your time.
[applause]
>> [snorts]
>> Good day, Bashar. And to you, good day.
>> I'm pretty excited to be here.
>> We are very excited that you are there.
>> Great. Bashar, you're really awful.
>> Full of awe.
>> Exactly.
Um, first of all, the most pressing
question was, how do you dance in your
society? Because you're still
quasphysical.
>> Yes.
>> Right.
>> Yes. So what does a dance look like?
>> It depends on the person and how they
feel they wish to move.
>> Mhm. Okay.
>> There's no real structured sense of
dancing.
>> People will dance as they wish to dance.
>> All right. And you said the music that
was mo you could compare it to mostly
was um the steel drum. And
>> it's very very simple. Mostly it's
percussive. There is some wind. There is
some string instruments but it's very
simplistic to you. Mhm.
>> But to us, we can hear many different
harmonies within what you would perceive
only as a single note.
>> So there aren't any drums.
>> Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> Simple drums. Okay. Yeah.
>> Different kinds. Not just the idea of
what you call steel. We don't really
have steel drums.
>> What is it made of then?
>> It is made of a crystallin nano
material.
>> Mhm. Okay. Uh, next question. Uh, last
year in August, I got stuck in a
machine.
>> Stuck in a machine? in a like well it
was an accident [laughter]
and it was pretty exciting. Uh I got
stuck on a conveyor belt. It squeezed my
leg.
>> Oh, all right.
>> And uh
>> and what popped out?
>> Oh, well. [laughter]
>> Well, a lot of stuff I didn't need. And
what was interesting about the
experience was that um at some point I
could see myself lying on the floor and
all the people around me helping me.
>> Yes.
>> Um
>> you had an elevated point of view.
>> Exactly. And it's it Yeah. It kind of I
could I could like be the person that
put on the movie instead of being the
person playing it.
>> And so what did that do for you in life?
>> Well, it taught me that uh I don't need
to uh go for jobs that pay a lot of
money.
But
>> go for what excites you and you will be
supported in whatever way you need to.
>> Did it also remove any kind of concept
that you have to be afraid of death?
>> Not quite.
>> No, not
>> you're still afraid of death. Is that
what you're saying?
>> Yeah.
>> Why? What are you afraid will happen?
>> You know that all of you die billions of
times a second. Well, that helps.
[laughter]
>> Not so bad, is it?
>> No, it's it's all right. Yeah.
>> Still here, aren't you?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. You will always change.
You're always dying. You're always being
reborn billions of times per second.
You're becoming a new person every
moment. Every moment, every moment,
every moment. Because you're shifting
your consciousness through billions of
parallel reality versions of yourself in
order to create the side effect you call
time and space and change.
>> Okay? So you're dying all the time. So
yet here you are.
>> So So what?
>> So So what
>> exactly? Okay.
>> The most powerful mantra you can have.
So what?
>> Yes. [laughter]
>> Yeah. That's a favorite.
[applause]
>> Does that help?
>> It does help. Yes.
>> All right.
>> Uh talking about mantras, I'm following
my excitement now and in about 3 weeks
I'll fly to India.
>> Oh, all right.
>> Go to the Himalayas. Yes.
>> And um is there anything you want to
tell me about that?
>> Have a good time.
>> Okay. Discover more of yourself.
>> Yes.
>> There may be a few things that will be
imparted to you by some of the people
that you meet. That will be some of the
information you've been looking for.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. I have a feeling there are some
people that want to meet me like looking
at the clock and like
>> Yes. Yes. Yes.
>> So, have fun.
>> Yes. One more question.
>> That was a question. Another one.
>> That was a question.
>> Another one.
>> Two more.
>> Okay.
Some of you are actually learning.
Um, so last year I was traveling to
Rotterdam with a friend and I looked out
in the in a train and I looked outside
the window and there was a a thing in
the air and it looked like the thing.
>> A thing. Yes.
>> What did the thing look like? like an
independence day the ship and I know
you're keeping schedule of all the ships
that are flying around. So, do you know
anything about it? [laughter]
No. Okay.
>> Thank you.
[applause]
>> We actually did, but we're not going to
tell him.
Just kidding.
You want to come up? Okay, here you go.
Um,
[sighs]
>> hello Bashar.
>> And to you, good day.
>> Um, for my profession, uh, I'm an
electronic and audio engineer.
>> And, uh, I have a major passion for
Tesla and Tesla technology and also
health technology. One of the things I'm
into is ozenated water and
electrotherapy.
Um I just wondered if you could
elaborate on those things and whether
they are a benefit to uh uh humanity.
Any permission slip that you're excited
about is a benefit to someone. So the
idea is always understand that all
tools, all techniques, all rituals, all
objects, no matter in what form they may
be created, if they are exciting to you,
if they are an expression of your
excitement, they will be a benefit to
someone. They may not necessarily
benefit everyone, but they will be a
benefit to someone because if it's a
gift you have to give, there is someone
waiting to receive it.
>> Okay. I thought you were going to say
that. Um, would you psychic?
>> Brilliant. Would you be able to
elaborate a little bit more on my uh my
interest actually on Tesla and the
connection there? Because I'm uh I've
been told by medium I have a connection
there, but I'm making a connection just
like anyone. and you are passionate
about something, you will make energetic
connections to other beings that you are
aware of or even some that you're not
aware of that may be similarly focused
and therefore you can download energy
and information from them to assist you
in exploring the theme and the passions
that you're following in this life. So
you make whatever connections you need
to to help guide you and propel you
forward on that path.
>> Brilliant. Uh one final question I
wanted to know, do I have any hybrid
children?
not directly in the way that you mean
it. You are involved peripherally in
another way that has to do with certain
educational things, but we won't go
deeply into that right now for a variety
of reasons that I can't go deeply into
right now. [laughter]
>> I understand. Uh, thank you very much
for your time.
Hello Bashar.
>> And you good day.
>> I'm very grateful to be to be here. I
love you and Darl and your melodic
voice.
>> Our unconditional love to you as well.
>> Thank [laughter] you. Uh one of my
profession in this in in this reality is
a musical composer.
>> Oh, all right. How exciting. I would
like to ask you uh please uh could you
explain um connection uh between sound
and matter or or mass? Uh I feel that uh
sound
creates um the the whole creation.
>> Yes. Well, everything is resonance.
Everything is frequency. Everything is a
vibration of existence itself. So all
the different frequencies determine the
things that you perceive as different
things. It's all made out of the same
thing. It's all made out of
consciousness. It's all made out of
existence. It's all one thing. But the
different vibrations, the different
resonances, the different frequencies
within it create the appearance and the
experience of different things,
including the concept of sound and
light. You can see that they are
interchangeable when you start to
discover as many of your scientists have
that you can transform one into the
other such as the science you know or
the effect you know as sonoluminescence.
You're familiar with this
>> where sound is used to create light.
>> Light?
>> Yes. It's called sonoluminescence.
Look it up. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
>> They have found a way on your planet to
use sound vibrations to actually create
light because it's just different
expressions of the same thing at
different frequencies.
>> Okay.
>> So, it's all about resonance. Yes.
>> Okay. Thank you very much. And could you
tell us about the full potential of
music for for our civilization?
Well, there are many ways to express it,
of course, and different individuals may
need to experience it in a variety of
different ways according to their belief
systems, according to the themes that
they're exploring and the path that they
are on. But generally speaking, you
could say that when you create the
resonances that are most aligned with
your true selves on an individual group
and collective level, you will immerse
yourselves in a bubble of vibration and
a bubble of resonance in a bubble
reality that will be conducive to
accelerating and amplifying you very
very powerfully.
This we do on our planet in a very
specific way. We have three spheres that
surround our planet that orbit our
planet. Each sphere is about 75 mi in
diameter. They resonate at a certain
frequency and immerse our planet in a
bubble energy that allows us more
ability to remain within a synchronistic
state. These three spheres are referred
to as epsilon, epiphany, and eclipse.
We don't have moons, but we have these
three spheres. They create an energy
bubble, a state of being that allows us
more opportunity to remain within the
synchronism that we experience in our
reality.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> So, it's similar to what you're talking
about.
>> Okay. Thank
>> Thank you. Thank you very much. You are
welcome very